let questions = [
    {   // QUESTION #1
        question: "Which colony was John Adams born in?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Virgnia",
        choiceB: "New York",
        choiceC: "Pennsylvania",
        choiceD: "Massachusetts",
        correct: "D"
    }, { // QUESTION #2
        question: "What was the profession of John Adams before the war?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Rope Maker",
        choiceB: "Lawyer",
        choiceC: "Ship Captain",
        choiceD: "Surveyor",
        correct: "B"
    },
    {   // QUESTION #3
        question: "John Adams defended british soldiers charged with murder in the Boston Massacre. Who was their captain?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Philip Schuyler",
        choiceB: "John Simcoe",
        choiceC: "Thomas Preston",
        choiceD: "William Prescott",
        correct: "C"
    }, { // QUESTION #4
        question: "What did Abigail Adams have their children innoculated with?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Big Pox",
        choiceB: "Small Pox",
        choiceC: "Malaria",
        choiceD: "Yellow Fever",
        correct: "B"
    }, { // QUESTION #5
        question: "On April 1st, 1778, John Adams arrived in this country as an ambassador:",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "France",
        choiceB: "Britain",
        choiceC: "Spain",
        choiceD: "Russia",
        correct: "A"
    }, { // QUESTION #6
        question: "On his first trip to France, John Adams brought which family member with him?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "His son Charles",
        choiceB: "His daughter Nabby",
        choiceC: "His son John",
        choiceD: "His wife Abigail",
        correct: "C"
    }, { // QUESTION #7
        question: "In 1782, John Adams travelled to this country to secure a loan and recognition of American independence:",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Netherlands",
        choiceB: "Spain",
        choiceC: "Russia",
        choiceD: "Italy",
        correct: "A"
    }, { // QUESTION #8
        question: "In 1783, John Adams signed this treaty that would end the Revolutionary War:",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Treaty of Versailles",
        choiceB: "Treaty of Ghent",
        choiceC: "Jay treaty",
        choiceD: "Treaty of Paris",
        correct: "D"
    }, { // QUESTION #9
        question: "In 1785, John Adams became the first U.S. minister to which country",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Mexico",
        choiceB: "Britain",
        choiceC: "China",
        choiceD: "Spain",
        correct: "B"
    }, { // QUESTION #10
        question: "Which political party did John Adams belong to?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Federalists",
        choiceB: "Anti Federalists",
        choiceC: "Whigs",
        choiceD: "Democrats",
        correct: "A"
    }
];